<Servers> 
    <ServerGroup Name="5thDay" Logo="https://www.jeffthepcguy.com/snj/5thday/5thdayheader.jpg" Description="5th Day My realistic approach to 7 days">
        <Server Name="5thDay" Logo="https://www.jeffthepcguy.com/snj/5thday/5thdayheader.jpg">
            <Description>
		Jeff had this weird thought that he should take the idea from Crystal Hell mod (Thanks Shavick) and build upon the learn by doing system. Then along the way was like. ok I don't like the workbechs let's make our own and change how you craft them, Then out of the blue was like I don't like the weapons and how you craft ammo let's change that too, etc.

Detailed well as detailed as I can make it lit of changes.
* Removed magazines
* Removed skills and skill points everything is learn by doing, using and some crafting
* Workbench crafting is changed. You need to find items or the workbench itself in the world and craft or repair from that.
* Some workbenchs require s-core wireless power. Basically have to have a battery bank or generator running within 10 blocks.
* Cooking requires a propane camp stove and black propane tank. Fueled by a white propane tank (can be found in large tanks)
* Bulleted weapons have a special way they need to be dealt with.
   + Pistols skill must be level 50+ to unlock the ability to use a machine gun or shotgun
   + Machine guns must be level 50+ to unlock the ability to use a SMG.
   + Shotguns must be level 50+ to unlock the ability to use a rifle.
* only way to level a weapon is to use it.
* We added a weighted backpack system thanks to s-core. there are 4 backpacks. Civilian aka starter. Small, Medium and Large military 
  backpacks each level increases your carrying capacity. These are crafted by leveling your armor skills. Leveling armor can be done a few ways. By crafting cloth, letting your armor take damage and lastly by crafting armor mods.
* Biome protection is a thing. Each biome has a so called biome boss. They are tied to your trader reputation. While in the forrest 
  biome when you reach level 10 or higher you have a 3% chance every 5 minutes to spawn the forrest boss.
  Each biome has a special ore. Forrest and burnt forrest is Nitrate. Desert is Oil shale and Snow is Iron. Make sure to read AOM V1.
* Speaking of trader rep. when you reach level 10 you also now have the ability to craft a trader Purchacing vending machine to place 
  in your base. Starting with trader Rekt.
* Time: time is a wonderful thing too bad you can't tell time. Waite loot a couch and see if you can find a blue cell phone.. Just 
  don't open it. you need it whole. Well atleast the first one.
* Added 2 new traps. A mid-evil spike trap as well as a oil slick.
Tons more alterations. Now i do not want to spoil anything or give to much away. In the real world you have to figure some things out on your own. I will tell you this thou... Yes there is alot of things you can loot. and yes you can make alot of coin and cash. But just about everything is needed in a recipe somewhere for something. So don't just go on a looting / selling spree.. you never know you just might need it for something.

            </Description>
           	
           	<Version>2.1</Version>
            <EAC>Disabled</EAC>
            <Discord>https://discord.gg/WuEVwMqj8e</Discord>
            <Donate></Donate>
            <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
            <Downloads>
                <Download>https://github.com/SarahandJeff/the5thday2.0</Download>
            </Downloads>

        </Server>
    </ServerGroup>
</Servers>